吼吼吼
Ho ho ho.
哦哦哦
No no no.
哥们儿  咋穿成这样
Dude, what's with the suit?
我计划着把圣诞啦啦队
I have a plan to turn Christmas cheer
变成圣诞收银台
into Christmas ka-ching.
我现在给你十五秒时间
Ka-ching just bought you 15 seconds.
你有什么点子
Impress me.
好吧  那个盛大的节日树灯晚会
Okay, so they do that holiday spectacular tree lighting ceremony
在里奇伍德高中旁的公园举行
n the park next to Ridgewood High.
但你知道他们缺什么吗
But do you know what they don't have?
再有7秒钟就没机会了
Seven more seconds to impress me?
圣诞老人驻扎点
A Santa stand.
可爱的孩子加上多愁善感的父母
Adorable kids plus sentimental parents
等于一叠叠的钞票啊
equals cold hard cash.
啊  你还真想了个好主意
Whoa. You actually had a good idea.
这绝对是圣诞奇迹
It's a Christmas miracle.
今年我花了太多钱买圣诞礼物
Well I spent too much on Christmas presents this year
我欠老爸一些钱
and I owe Dad some money.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help. So...
你要加入吗
You in?
和朋友要亲密 和你的坏哥哥要更亲密
Keep your friends close and your jerky brother closer.
要是我只有弄坏那个直升机才能玩
If I can't play with the helicopter until I break it,
那我就不玩儿死乔伊就誓不罢休
I'm gonna play with Joey until I break him.
在平安夜和我大哥一起小聚
A little quality time with my big bro on Christmas Eve?
行吧
You bet.